<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Planto</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter email</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter password</string>
    <string name="error_while_logging_in">Error while logging in</string>
    <string name="registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter name</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <!-- Preference Titles -->

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->

    <string name="key_upload_quality">key_upload_quality</string>
    <string name="remind_me_for_the_check_time">remind_me_for_the_check_time</string>
    <string name="remind_for_the_check_time">Remind me for the check time</string>
    <string name="limit_data_usage">prefs_limit_data_usage</string>
    <string name="stream_video">Only stream HD video on Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="limit_mobile_usage">Limit mobile data usage</string>
    <string name="uploads">Uploads</string>
    <string name="pref_uploads">pref_uploads</string>
    <string name="specify_network_prefs">Specify network preferences for uploads</string>
    <string name="prefs_restricted_mode">prefs_restricted_mode</string>
    <string name="restricated_mode">Restricted Mode can help to hide videos with potentially mature content.No filter is 100% accurate, but it should help you to avoid most of this type of content.</string>
    <string name="restricated_mode_description">Restricted Mode</string>
    <string name="prefs_enable_stats">prefs_enable_stats</string>
    <string name="enable_stats">Enable stats for nerds</string>
    <string name="start">start</string>


    <string-array name="pref_remind_me_to_come_back_later">
        <item>1 hours</item>
        <item>2 hours</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>5 hours</item>
        <item>10 hours</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pref_duration">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pref_uploads">
        <item>Only when on Wi-Fi</item>
        <item>Only when on 4G</item>
        <item>On any network</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="model_spinner">
        <item>Fruits</item>
        <item>Ornamentals</item>
        <item>Flowers</item>
        <item>Pests</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Plant Disease Classes -->
    <string-array name="plant_disease_classes">
        <item>Apple__black_rot</item>
        <item>Apple__healthy</item>
        <item>Apple__rust</item>
        <item>Apple__scab</item>
        <item>Background_without_leaves</item>
        <item>Cassava__bacterial_blight</item>
        <item>Cassava__brown_streak_disease</item>
        <item>Cassava__green_mottle</item>
        <item>Cassava__healthy</item>
        <item>Cassava__mosaic_disease</item>
        <item>Cherry__healthy</item>
        <item>Cherry__powdery_mildew</item>
        <item>Chili__healthy</item>
        <item>Chili__leaf curl</item>
        <item>Chili__leaf spot</item>
        <item>Chili__whitefly</item>
        <item>Chili__yellowish</item>
        <item>Coffee__cercospora_leaf_spot</item>
        <item>Coffee__healthy</item>
        <item>Coffee__red_spider_mite</item>
        <item>Coffee__rust</item>
        <item>Corn__common_rust</item>
        <item>Corn__gray_leaf_spot</item>
        <item>Corn__healthy</item>
        <item>Corn__northern_leaf_blight</item>
        <item>Cucumber__diseased</item>
        <item>Cucumber__healthy</item>
        <item>Gauva__diseased</item>
        <item>Gauva__healthy</item>
        <item>Grape__black_measles</item>
        <item>Grape__black_rot</item>
        <item>Grape__healthy</item>
        <item>Grape__leaf_blight</item>
        <item>Jamun__diseased</item>
        <item>Jamun__healthy</item>
        <item>Lemon__diseased</item>
        <item>Lemon__healthy</item>
        <item>Mango__diseased</item>
        <item>Mango__healthy</item>
        <item>Peach__bacterial_spot</item>
        <item>Peach__healthy</item>
        <item>Pepper_bell__bacterial_spot</item>
        <item>Pepper_bell__healthy</item>
        <item>Pomegranate__diseased</item>
        <item>Pomegranate__healthy</item>
        <item>Potato__early_blight</item>
        <item>Potato__healthy</item>
        <item>Potato__late_blight</item>
        <item>Rice__brown_spot</item>
        <item>Rice__healthy</item>
        <item>Rice__hispa</item>
        <item>Rice__leaf_blast</item>
        <item>Rice__neck_blast</item>
        <item>Soybean__bacterial_blight</item>
        <item>Soybean__caterpillar</item>
        <item>Soybean__diabrotica_speciosa</item>
        <item>Soybean__downy_mildew</item>
        <item>Soybean__healthy</item>
        <item>Soybean__mosaic_virus</item>
        <item>Soybean__powdery_mildew</item>
        <item>Soybean__rust</item>
        <item>Soybean__southern_blight</item>
        <item>Strawberry___leaf_scorch</item>
        <item>Strawberry__healthy</item>
        <item>Sugarcane__bacterial_blight</item>
        <item>Sugarcane__healthy</item>
        <item>Sugarcane__red_rot</item>
        <item>Sugarcane__red_stripe</item>
        <item>Sugarcane__rust</item>
        <item>Tea__algal_leaf</item>
        <item>Tea__anthracnose</item>
        <item>Tea__bird_eye_spot</item>
        <item>Tea__brown_blight</item>
        <item>Tea__healthy</item>
        <item>Tea__red_leaf_spot</item>
        <item>Tomato__bacterial_spot</item>
        <item>Tomato__early_blight</item>
        <item>Tomato__healthy</item>
        <item>Tomato__late_blight</item>
        <item>Tomato__leaf_mold</item>
        <item>Tomato__mosaic_virus</item>
        <item>Tomato__septoria_leaf_spot</item>
        <item>Tomato__spider_mites_(two_spotted_spider_mite)</item>
        <item>Tomato__target_spot</item>
        <item>Tomato__yellow_leaf_curl_virus</item>
        <item>Wheat__brown_rust</item>
        <item>Wheat__healthy</item>
        <item>Wheat__septoria</item>
        <item>Wheat__yellow_rust</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Precautions -->
    <string name="Description_1"><![CDATA[<h1>Black Rot in Apple</h1><p>Black Rot is a fungal disease that affects apple trees, causing damage to the fruit and foliage. To prevent and manage black rot, follow these steps:</p>]]></string>
    <!-- Precautions -->
    <string name="Apple__black_rot"><![CDATA[<h1>Black Rot in Apple</h1><p>Black Rot is a fungal disease that affects apple trees, causing damage to the fruit and foliage. To prevent and manage black rot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Remove and destroy infected fruit and plant debris.</li><li>Step 2: Prune affected branches to improve air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Maintain proper tree nutrition and watering practices.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor and scout for early signs of black rot.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Apple__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Apple</h1><p>Your apple tree appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide adequate water and nutrients to the tree.</li><li>Step 2: Prune and remove dead or diseased branches regularly.</li><li>Step 3: Monitor for pests and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 4: Maintain a clean and well-ventilated growing environment.</li><li>Step 5: Follow good agricultural practices for apple cultivation.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Apple__rust"><![CDATA[<h1>Rust in Apple</h1><p>Rust is a fungal disease that affects apple trees, causing orange-brown spots on leaves and fruit. To prevent and manage rust, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 2: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 3: Improve air circulation around the tree by proper pruning.</li><li>Step 4: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the tree at the base.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the tree for early signs of rust and take prompt action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Apple__scab"><![CDATA[<h1>Scab in Apple</h1><p>Scab is a fungal disease that affects apple trees, causing dark, scaly lesions on leaves, fruit, and twigs. To prevent and manage scab, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Remove and destroy infected leaves and fruit.</li><li>Step 2: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 3: Prune affected branches to improve air circulation and light penetration.</li><li>Step 4: Maintain proper tree nutrition and watering practices.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the tree for scab symptoms and take appropriate action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Background_without_leaves"><![CDATA[<h1>Background without Leaves</h1><p>This is a background image without any specific plant disease. Use this image when no disease is detected or to represent a healthy plant.</p>]]></string>

    <string name="Cassava__bacterial_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Bacterial Blight in Cassava</h1><p>Bacterial blight is a common disease in cassava, characterized by dark, water-soaked lesions on leaves and stems. To prevent and manage bacterial blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free cassava cuttings obtained from reliable sources.</li><li>Step 2: Remove and destroy infected plant parts, including leaves and stems.</li><li>Step 3: Apply copper-based or other recommended bactericides.</li><li>Step 4: Maintain proper spacing between cassava plants for good airflow.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation and avoid planting cassava in the same area repeatedly.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Cassava__brown_streak_disease"><![CDATA[<h1>Brown Streak Disease in Cassava</h1><p>Brown streak disease is a viral infection that affects cassava, causing yellow or brown streaks on leaves and roots. To prevent and manage brown streak disease, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free cassava varieties obtained from reputable sources.</li><li>Step 2: Control whiteflies, which transmit the virus, using insecticides or biological control methods.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected cassava plants and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Ensure proper soil fertility and irrigation for healthy plant growth.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the field regularly for early signs of the disease and take appropriate measures.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Cassava__green_mottle"><![CDATA[<h1>Green Mottle in Cassava</h1><p>Green mottle is a viral disease that affects cassava, causing mottled or mosaic patterns on leaves. To prevent and manage green mottle, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free cassava cuttings obtained from reliable sources.</li><li>Step 2: Control whiteflies, which transmit the virus, using insecticides or biological control methods.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected cassava plants and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good weed control to prevent alternative hosts for the virus.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the cassava field regularly for signs of the disease and take appropriate action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Cassava__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Cassava</h1><p>Your cassava plants appear to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free cassava cuttings from reliable sources.</li><li>Step 2: Ensure proper soil fertility and irrigation for healthy plant growth.</li><li>Step 3: Control pests, such as whiteflies and mealybugs, using appropriate methods.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good weed control to reduce competition and disease risks.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the cassava field regularly for any signs of diseases or pests.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Cassava__mosaic_disease"><![CDATA[<h1>Mosaic Disease in Cassava</h1><p>Mosaic disease is a viral infection that affects cassava, causing mosaic patterns and stunted growth. To prevent and manage mosaic disease, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free cassava varieties obtained from reputable sources.</li><li>Step 2: Control whiteflies, which transmit the virus, using insecticides or biological control methods.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected cassava plants and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good weed control to reduce alternative hosts for the virus.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the cassava field regularly for early signs of the disease and take appropriate measures.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Cherry__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Cherry</h1><p>Your cherry tree appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Prune and remove dead or diseased branches regularly.</li><li>Step 2: Provide adequate water and nutrients to the tree.</li><li>Step 3: Monitor for pests, such as aphids and cherry fruit flies, and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides or other disease control measures as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and fruit to prevent disease spread.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Cherry__powdery_mildew"><![CDATA[<h1>Powdery Mildew in Cherry</h1><p>Powdery mildew is a fungal disease that affects cherry trees, causing a powdery white coating on leaves and fruit. To prevent and manage powdery mildew, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant resistant cherry varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between cherry trees for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected leaves and fruit.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the cherry trees regularly for signs of powdery mildew and take prompt action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Chili__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Chili</h1><p>Your chili plants appear to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide adequate sunlight, water, and nutrients for chili plants.</li><li>Step 2: Practice proper spacing between plants to ensure good airflow.</li><li>Step 3: Monitor for pests, such as aphids and mites, and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides or other disease control measures as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Harvest chili peppers at the appropriate time to avoid overripening and disease susceptibility.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Chili__leaf_curl"><![CDATA[<h1>Leaf Curl in Chili</h1><p>Leaf curl is a viral disease that affects chili plants, causing curling and distortion of leaves. To prevent and manage leaf curl, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant chili varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Control whiteflies, which transmit the virus, using insecticides or biological control methods.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected chili plants and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good weed control to reduce alternative hosts for the virus.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the chili plants regularly for signs of leaf curl and take appropriate action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Chili__leaf_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Leaf Spot in Chili</h1><p>Leaf spot is a fungal disease that affects chili plants, causing circular or irregular spots on leaves. To prevent and manage leaf spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between chili plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the chili plants regularly for signs of leaf spot and take prompt action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Chili__whitefly"><![CDATA[<h1>Whitefly Infestation in Chili</h1><p>Whiteflies are common pests that infest chili plants, causing yellowing, stunted growth, and honeydew secretion. To prevent and manage whitefly infestation, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Monitor the plants regularly for signs of whiteflies.</li><li>Step 2: Introduce natural predators, such as ladybugs or parasitic wasps, to control whitefly populations.</li><li>Step 3: Use yellow sticky traps to catch adult whiteflies.</li><li>Step 4: Apply insecticidal soap or neem oil to control severe infestations.</li><li>Step 5: Remove and destroy heavily infested leaves or plants if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Chili__yellowish"><![CDATA[<h1>Yellowing in Chili Plants</h1><p>Yellowing of chili plants can be caused by various factors, including nutrient deficiencies, overwatering, or pests. To prevent and manage yellowing in chili plants, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Ensure proper watering practices, allowing the soil to dry slightly between waterings.</li><li>Step 2: Provide adequate sunlight for the chili plants.</li><li>Step 3: Check for nutrient deficiencies and supplement with appropriate fertilizers.</li><li>Step 4: Monitor for pests and take necessary pest control measures.</li><li>Step 5: Avoid over-fertilization, as it can lead to nutrient imbalances and yellowing of leaves.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Coffee__cercospora_leaf_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Cercospora Leaf Spot in Coffee</h1><p>Cercospora leaf spot is a fungal disease that affects coffee plants, causing small, dark spots on leaves. To prevent and manage cercospora leaf spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide adequate shade and air circulation for the coffee plants.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and maintaining a clean growing area.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Coffee__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Coffee Plant</h1><p>Your coffee plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide adequate shade and sunlight for optimal growth.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plant regularly, allowing the soil to dry slightly between waterings.</li><li>Step 3: Fertilize the plant with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Prune the plant to maintain its shape and promote airflow.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Coffee__red_spider_mite"><![CDATA[<h1>Red Spider Mite Infestation in Coffee</h1><p>Red spider mites are common pests that infest coffee plants, causing yellowing, stippling, and webbing on leaves. To prevent and manage red spider mite infestation, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Monitor the plants regularly for signs of red spider mites.</li><li>Step 2: Increase humidity around the plants by misting them or using a humidifier.</li><li>Step 3: Apply insecticidal soap or neem oil to control severe infestations.</li><li>Step 4: Introduce predatory mites or other natural enemies to control mite populations.</li><li>Step 5: Remove and destroy heavily infested leaves or plants if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Coffee__rust"><![CDATA[<h1>Coffee Rust</h1><p>Coffee rust is a fungal disease that affects coffee plants, causing orange or yellowish rust-like spots on leaves. To prevent and manage coffee rust, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide adequate shade and air circulation for the coffee plants.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and maintaining a clean growing area.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Corn__common_rust"><![CDATA[<h1>Common Rust in Corn</h1><p>Common rust is a fungal disease that affects corn plants, causing reddish-brown pustules on leaves. To prevent and manage common rust, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant corn varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Practice crop rotation and avoid planting corn in consecutive years.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor for early signs of rust and take preventive action accordingly.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Corn__gray_leaf_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Gray Leaf Spot in Corn</h1><p>Gray leaf spot is a fungal disease that affects corn plants, causing grayish lesions on leaves. To prevent and manage gray leaf spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant corn varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide adequate spacing between plants to promote airflow.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation and avoid planting corn in consecutive years.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Corn__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Corn Plant</h1><p>Your corn plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant corn varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide adequate spacing between plants for optimal growth.</li><li>Step 3: Water the plants regularly, ensuring sufficient moisture but avoiding overwatering.</li><li>Step 4: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation and avoid planting corn in consecutive years.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Corn__northern_leaf_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Northern Leaf Blight in Corn</h1><p>Northern leaf blight is a fungal disease that affects corn plants, causing elongated tan lesions on leaves. To prevent and manage northern leaf blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant corn varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide adequate spacing between plants to promote airflow.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation and avoid planting corn in consecutive years.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Cucumber__diseased"><![CDATA[<h1>Disease in Cucumber Plants</h1><p>Cucumber plants can be affected by various diseases, including fungal infections and bacterial diseases. To prevent and manage diseases in cucumber plants, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants at the base and avoid wetting the foliage excessively.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant parts.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides or bactericides as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation and avoid planting cucumbers in consecutive years.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Cucumber__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Cucumber Plant</h1><p>Your cucumber plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants at the base and avoid wetting the foliage excessively.</li><li>Step 3: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 5: Harvest cucumbers promptly to prevent overripening and disease development.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Gauva__diseased"><![CDATA[<h1>Disease in Guava Plants</h1><p>Guava plants can be affected by various diseases, including fungal infections, bacterial diseases, and viruses. To prevent and manage diseases in guava plants, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants at the base and avoid wetting the foliage excessively.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant parts.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides or bactericides as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and maintaining a clean growing area.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Gauva__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Guava Plant</h1><p>Your guava plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants regularly, ensuring sufficient moisture but avoiding overwatering.</li><li>Step 3: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 5: Prune the plant to maintain its shape and promote airflow.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Grape__black_measles"><![CDATA[<h1>Black Measles in Grapevines</h1><p>Black measles, also known as black rot, is a fungal disease that affects grapevines, causing black lesions on leaves, stems, and fruits. To prevent and manage black measles, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant grapevine varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between vines for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Prune the vines to improve airflow and sunlight penetration.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant parts, including fallen leaves and fruit mummies.</li><li>Step 5: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Grape__black_rot"><![CDATA[<h1>Black Rot in Grapevines</h1><p>Black rot is a fungal disease that affects grapevines, causing black lesions on leaves, stems, and fruits. To prevent and manage black rot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant grapevine varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between vines for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Prune the vines to improve airflow and sunlight penetration.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant parts, including fallen leaves and fruit mummies.</li><li>Step 5: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Grape__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Grapevine</h1><p>Your grapevine appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between vines for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Prune the vines to improve airflow and sunlight penetration.</li><li>Step 3: Water the plants at the base and avoid wetting the foliage excessively.</li><li>Step 4: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Grape__leaf_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Leaf Blight (Isariopsis Leaf Spot) in Grapevines</h1><p>Leaf blight, also known as Isariopsis leaf spot, is a fungal disease that affects grapevines, causing brown lesions on leaves. To prevent and manage leaf blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant grapevine varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between vines for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Prune the vines to improve airflow and sunlight penetration.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant parts, including fallen leaves.</li><li>Step 5: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Jamun__diseased"><![CDATA[<h1>Disease in Jamun Plants</h1><p>Jamun plants can be affected by various diseases, including fungal infections, bacterial diseases, and viruses. To prevent and manage diseases in jamun plants, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants at the base and avoid wetting the foliage excessively.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant parts.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides or bactericides as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and maintaining a clean growing area.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Jamun__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Jamun Plant</h1><p>Your jamun plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants regularly, ensuring sufficient moisture but avoiding overwatering.</li><li>Step 3: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 5: Prune the plant to maintain its shape and promote airflow.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Lemon__diseased"><![CDATA[<h1>Disease in Lemon Plants</h1><p>Lemon plants can be affected by various diseases, including fungal infections, bacterial diseases, and viral infections. To prevent and manage diseases in lemon plants, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants at the base and avoid wetting the foliage excessively.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant parts.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides or bactericides as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and maintaining a clean growing area.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Lemon__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Lemon Plant</h1><p>Your lemon plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants regularly, ensuring sufficient moisture but avoiding overwatering.</li><li>Step 3: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 5: Prune the plant to maintain its shape and promote airflow.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Mango__diseased"><![CDATA[<h1>Disease in Mango Plants</h1><p>Mango plants can be affected by various diseases, including fungal infections, bacterial diseases, and viral infections. To prevent and manage diseases in mango plants, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants at the base and avoid wetting the foliage excessively.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant parts.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides or bactericides as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and maintaining a clean growing area.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Mango__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Mango Plant</h1><p>Your mango plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants regularly, ensuring sufficient moisture but avoiding overwatering.</li><li>Step 3: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 5: Prune the plant to maintain its shape and promote airflow.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Peach__bacterial_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Bacterial Spot in Peach Trees</h1><p>Bacterial spot is a common disease that affects peach trees, causing dark lesions on leaves, fruit, and stems. To prevent and manage bacterial spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant peach tree varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between trees for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Prune the trees to improve airflow and sunlight penetration.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant parts, including fallen leaves and fruit.</li><li>Step 5: Apply copper-based bactericides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Peach__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Peach Tree</h1><p>Your peach tree appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between trees for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Prune the trees to improve airflow and sunlight penetration.</li><li>Step 3: Water the plants deeply and infrequently, allowing the soil to dry out between waterings.</li><li>Step 4: Fertilize the trees with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Pepper_bell__bacterial_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Bacterial Spot in Bell Peppers</h1><p>Bacterial spot is a common disease that affects bell pepper plants, causing dark lesions on leaves, fruit, and stems. To prevent and manage bacterial spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant bell pepper varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Prune the plants to improve airflow and sunlight penetration.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant parts, including fallen leaves and fruit.</li><li>Step 5: Apply copper-based bactericides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Pepper_bell__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Bell Pepper Plant</h1><p>Your bell pepper plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Prune the plants to improve airflow and sunlight penetration.</li><li>Step 3: Water the plants deeply and infrequently, allowing the soil to dry out between waterings.</li><li>Step 4: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Pomegranate__diseased"><![CDATA[<h1>Disease in Pomegranate Plants</h1><p>Pomegranate plants can be affected by various diseases, including fungal infections, bacterial diseases, and viral infections. To prevent and manage diseases in pomegranate plants, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants at the base and avoid wetting the foliage excessively.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant parts.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides or bactericides as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and maintaining a clean growing area.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Pomegranate__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Pomegranate Plant</h1><p>Your pomegranate plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants regularly, ensuring sufficient moisture but avoiding overwatering.</li><li>Step 3: Fertilize the plants with a balanced fertilizer according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 5: Prune the plant to maintain its shape and promote airflow.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Potato__early_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Early Blight in Potato Plants</h1><p>Early blight is a common fungal disease that affects potato plants, causing brown lesions on leaves, stems, and tubers. To prevent and manage early blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant potato varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant parts, including fallen leaves.</li><li>Step 4: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 5: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Potato__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Potato Plant</h1><p>Your potato plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants regularly, ensuring sufficient moisture but avoiding overwatering.</li><li>Step 3: Hill up the soil around the plants to promote tuber development.</li><li>Step 4: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 5: Harvest the potatoes at the right time to prevent storage diseases.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Potato__late_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Late Blight in Potato Plants</h1><p>Late blight is a devastating fungal disease that affects potato plants, causing dark lesions on leaves, stems, and tubers. To prevent and manage late blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant potato varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant parts, including fallen leaves.</li><li>Step 4: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 5: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Rice__brown_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Brown Spot in Rice Plants</h1><p>Brown spot is a common fungal disease that affects rice plants, causing brown lesions on leaves and sheaths. To prevent and manage brown spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant rice varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Avoid excessive nitrogen fertilizer, as it can promote disease development.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good water management and avoid over-irrigation.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Rice__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Rice Plant</h1><p>Your rice plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant rice varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Apply balanced fertilizers according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good water management, ensuring sufficient but not excessive irrigation.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Rice__hispa"><![CDATA[<h1>Hispa Infestation in Rice Plants</h1><p>Hispa is a common insect pest that affects rice plants, causing damage to leaves and reducing yield. To prevent and manage hispa infestation, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant rice varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Monitor for hispa adults and larvae and take action if their population exceeds the economic threshold.</li><li>Step 4: Apply appropriate insecticides as recommended.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Rice__leaf_blast"><![CDATA[<h1>Leaf Blast in Rice Plants</h1><p>Leaf blast is a common fungal disease that affects rice plants, causing lesions on leaves, stems, and panicles. To prevent and manage leaf blast, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant rice varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Apply balanced fertilizers according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides as recommended, especially during periods of high disease pressure.</li><li>Step 5: Drain fields properly and avoid excessive waterlogging, as it can promote disease development.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Rice__neck_blast"><![CDATA[<h1>Neck Blast in Rice Plants</h1><p>Neck blast is a fungal disease that affects rice plants, causing damage to the neck region of the panicles. To prevent and manage neck blast, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant rice varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Apply balanced fertilizers according to the recommended dosage.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides as recommended, especially during periods of high disease pressure.</li><li>Step 5: Drain fields properly and avoid excessive waterlogging, as it can promote disease development.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__bacterial_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Bacterial Blight in Soybean Plants</h1><p>Bacterial blight is a common disease that affects soybean plants, causing angular necrotic lesions on leaves, stems, and pods. To prevent and manage bacterial blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant soybean varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Practice crop rotation to reduce the buildup of bacterial populations in the soil.</li><li>Step 3: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Apply copper-based bactericides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__caterpillar"><![CDATA[<h1>Caterpillar Infestation in Soybean Plants</h1><p>Caterpillars are common insect pests that feed on soybean plants, causing defoliation and yield loss. To prevent and manage caterpillar infestations, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Monitor for caterpillar eggs and larvae and take action if their population exceeds the economic threshold.</li><li>Step 2: Apply appropriate insecticides as recommended.</li><li>Step 3: Implement cultural control methods such as planting early or using trap crops.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li><li>Step 5: Consider biological control methods using natural predators or parasites.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__diabrotica_speciosa"><![CDATA[<h1>Diabrotica speciosa Infestation in Soybean Plants</h1><p>Diabrotica speciosa, commonly known as the soybean leaf beetle, is a major pest of soybean plants. To prevent and manage Diabrotica speciosa infestations, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Monitor for adult beetles and their feeding damage.</li><li>Step 2: Implement cultural control methods such as planting early or using trap crops.</li><li>Step 3: Apply appropriate insecticides as recommended.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li><li>Step 5: Consider biological control methods using natural predators or parasites.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__downy_mildew"><![CDATA[<h1>Downy Mildew in Soybean Plants</h1><p>Downy mildew is a fungal disease that affects soybean plants, causing yellowish-green lesions on leaves and reducing yield. To prevent and manage downy mildew, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant soybean varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation to reduce the buildup of fungal populations in the soil.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Soybean Plant</h1><p>Your soybean plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide adequate water and nutrients to promote plant vigor.</li><li>Step 2: Monitor for any signs of pests or diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 3: Practice good field hygiene by removing weeds and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Follow recommended cultural practices for soybean cultivation.</li><li>Step 5: Consult with local agricultural extension services for specific recommendations in your area.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__mosaic_virus"><![CDATA[<h1>Mosaic Virus in Soybean Plants</h1><p>Mosaic virus is a viral disease that affects soybean plants, causing mottling and distortion of leaves. To prevent and manage mosaic virus, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant soybean varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Control aphid populations, as they can transmit the virus.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plants to prevent further spread.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts.</li><li>Step 5: Implement crop rotation to reduce the risk of virus buildup in the soil.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__powdery_mildew"><![CDATA[<h1>Powdery Mildew in Soybean Plants</h1><p>Powdery mildew is a fungal disease that affects soybean plants, causing white powdery patches on leaves and pods. To prevent and manage powdery mildew, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant soybean varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation to reduce the buildup of fungal populations in the soil.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__rust"><![CDATA[<h1>Rust in Soybean Plants</h1><p>Rust is a fungal disease that affects soybean plants, causing reddish-brown pustules on leaves, stems, and pods. To prevent and manage rust, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant soybean varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Practice crop rotation to reduce the buildup of fungal populations in the soil.</li><li>Step 5: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Soybean__southern_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Southern Blight in Soybean Plants</h1><p>Southern blight is a fungal disease that affects soybean plants, causing wilting, rotting, and stem girdling. To prevent and manage southern blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant soybean varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Practice proper crop rotation to reduce the risk of disease buildup.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Provide proper drainage to avoid waterlogging.</li><li>Step 5: Applyappropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Strawberry___leaf_scorch"><![CDATA[<h1>Leaf Scorch in Strawberry Plants</h1><p>Leaf scorch is a common disease that affects strawberry plants, causing browning and necrosis of leaf edges. To prevent and manage leaf scorch, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant strawberry varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Strawberry__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Strawberry Plant</h1><p>Your strawberry plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide adequate sunlight and water for optimal plant growth.</li><li>Step 2: Mulch around the plants to conserve moisture and suppress weeds.</li><li>Step 3: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 4: Prune runners and maintain good plant spacing for proper air circulation.</li><li>Step 5: Follow recommended fertilization practices for strawberry plants.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Sugarcane__bacterial_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Bacterial Blight in Sugarcane Plants</h1><p>Bacterial blight is a common disease that affects sugarcane plants, causing elliptical water-soaked lesions on leaves and stems. To prevent and manage bacterial blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free and healthy sugarcane seedlings.</li><li>Step 2: Implement crop rotation to reduce the risk of disease buildup.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Practice proper irrigation and avoid waterlogging.</li><li>Step 5: Apply copper-based bactericides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Sugarcane__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Sugarcane Plant</h1><p>Your sugarcane plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free and healthy sugarcane seedlings.</li><li>Step 2: Implement proper irrigation and drainage practices.</li><li>Step 3: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li><li>Step 4: Follow recommended fertilization practices for sugarcane.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Sugarcane__red_rot"><![CDATA[<h1>Red Rot in Sugarcane Plants</h1><p>Red rot is a fungal disease that affects sugarcane plants, causing reddish-brown discoloration and decay of internodes. To prevent and manage red rot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free and healthy sugarcane seedlings.</li><li>Step 2: Implement crop rotation to reduce the risk of disease buildup.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Practice proper irrigation and avoid waterlogging.</li><li>Step 5: Apply appropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Sugarcane__red_stripe"><![CDATA[<h1>Red Stripe in Sugarcane Plants</h1><p>Red stripe is a fungal disease that affects sugarcane plants, causing red discoloration of leaf sheaths and internodes. To prevent and manage red stripe, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-free and healthy sugarcane seedlings.</li><li>Step 2: Implement crop rotation to reduce the risk of disease buildup.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Practice proper irrigation and avoid waterlogging.</li><li>Step 5: Apply appropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Sugarcane__rust"><![CDATA[<h1>Rust in Sugarcane Plants</h1><p>Rust is a fungal disease that affects sugarcane plants, causing orange-brown pustules on leaves and stems. To prevent and manage rust, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant sugarcane varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Implement crop rotation to reduce the risk of disease buildup.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Apply appropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice proper irrigation and avoid waterlogging.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tea__algal_leaf"><![CDATA[<h1>Algal Leaf Spot in Tea Plants</h1><p>Algal leaf spot is a common disease that affects tea plants, causing dark green to black spots on leaves. To prevent and manage algal leaf spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between tea plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Apply appropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tea__anthracnose"><![CDATA[<h1>Anthracnose in Tea Plants</h1><p>Anthracnose is a fungal disease that affects tea plants, causing dark brown to black lesions on leaves, stems, and buds. To prevent and manage anthracnose, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between tea plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Apply appropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tea__bird_eye_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Bird\'s Eye Spot in Tea Plants</h1><p>Bird\'s eye spot is a fungal disease thataffects tea plants, causing circular or oval spots with a characteristic "bird's eye" appearance. To prevent and manage bird\'s eye spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between tea plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Apply appropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tea__brown_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Brown Blight in Tea Plants</h1><p>Brown blight is a fungal disease that affects tea plants, causing browning and wilting of leaves and shoots. To prevent and manage brown blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between tea plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Apply appropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tea__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Tea Plant</h1><p>Your tea plant appears to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide adequate sunlight and water for optimal plant growth.</li><li>Step 2: Prune the plants regularly to maintain good shape and airflow.</li><li>Step 3: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Follow recommended fertilization practices for tea plants.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor for pests and diseases and take appropriate action if necessary.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tea__red_leaf_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Red Leaf Spot in Tea Plants</h1><p>Red leaf spot is a common disease that affects tea plants, causing reddish-brown lesions on leaves. To prevent and manage red leaf spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between tea plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Apply appropriate fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good field hygiene by removing weed hosts and alternate host plants.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tomato__bacterial_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Bacterial Spot in Tomato</h1><p>Bacterial spot is a common disease in tomatoes, characterized by dark, water-soaked lesions on leaves and fruit. To prevent and manage bacterial spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant tomato varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between tomato plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 4: Apply copper-based or other recommended bactericides.</li><li>Step 5: Remove and destroy infected leaves and fruit to prevent disease spread.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tomato__early_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Early Blight in Tomato</h1><p>Early blight is a fungal disease that affects tomato plants, causing dark lesions on leaves and fruit. To prevent and manage early blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between tomato plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Mulch around the plants to prevent soil splashing and reduce disease spread.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the tomato plants regularly for signs of early blight and take prompt action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tomato__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Tomato</h1><p>Your tomato plants appear to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper support and trellising for tomato plants.</li><li>Step 2: Ensure adequate sunlight, water, and nutrients for healthy plant growth.</li><li>Step 3: Monitor for pests, such as aphids and tomato hornworms, and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good sanitation by removing fallen leaves and fruit to prevent disease spread.</li><li>Step 5: Follow recommended pruning techniques for optimal plant health and productivity.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tomato__late_blight"><![CDATA[<h1>Late Blight in Tomato</h1><p>Late blight is a devastating fungal disease that affects tomato plants, causing dark lesions on leaves, stems, and fruit. To prevent and manage late blight, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant tomato varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide proper spacing between tomato plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 3: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 4: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 5: Remove and destroy infected leaves, stems, and fruit to prevent disease spread.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tomato__leaf_mold"><![CDATA[<h1>Leaf Mold in Tomato</h1><p>Leaf mold is a fungal disease that affects tomato plants, causing yellowing and brown patches on leaves. To prevent and manage leaf mold, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between tomato plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Water the plants at the base and avoid overhead irrigation.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Mulch around the plants to prevent soil splashing and reduce disease spread.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tomato__spider_mites"><![CDATA[<h1>Spider Mites on Tomato</h1><p>Spider mites are common pests that affect tomato plants, causing yellowing, stippling, and webbing on leaves. To prevent and manage spider mites, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Monitor the plants regularly for signs of spider mites.</li><li>Step 2: Spray plants with a strong stream of water to dislodge mites.</li><li>Step 3: Apply insecticidal soap or horticultural oil to control severe infestations.</li><li>Step 4: Introduce natural predators, such as predatory mites or ladybugs, to control mite populations.</li><li>Step 5: Practice good sanitation by removing infested leaves and plant debris.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tomato__target_spot"><![CDATA[<h1>Target Spot in Tomato</h1><p>Target spot is a fungal disease that affects tomato plants, causing dark circular lesions with concentric rings on leaves and fruit. To prevent and manage target spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Provide proper spacing between tomato plants for good air circulation.</li><li>Step 2: Remove and destroy infected leaves and plant debris.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Avoid overhead irrigation and water the plants at the base.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the tomato plants regularly for signs of target spot and take prompt action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Tomato__yellow_leaf_curl_virus"><![CDATA[<h1>Yellow Leaf Curl Virus in Tomato</h1><p>Yellow leaf curl virus is a viral disease that affects tomato plants, causing curling and yellowing of leaves. To prevent and manage yellow leaf curl virus, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant tomato varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Control whiteflies, which transmit the virus, using insecticides or biological control methods.</li><li>Step 3: Remove and destroy infected tomato plants and plant debris.</li><li>Step 4: Practice good weed control to reduce alternative hosts for the virus.</li><li>Step 5: Monitor the tomato plants regularly for signs of yellow leaf curl virus and take appropriate action.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Wheat__brown_rust"><![CDATA[<h1>Brown Rust in Wheat</h1><p>Brown rust is a fungal disease that affects wheat plants, causing orange-brown pustules on leaves, stems, and grains. To prevent and manage brown rust, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant wheat varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid excessive nitrogen fertilization, as it can increase disease susceptibility.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Rotate wheat crops with non-host crops to break the disease cycle.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Wheat__healthy"><![CDATA[<h1>Healthy Wheat</h1><p>Your wheat plants appear to be healthy. However, it is essential to continue proper care and monitoring to prevent potential diseases. Here are some general tips:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant wheat varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Provide adequate soil fertility and balanced nutrition for healthy plant growth.</li><li>Step 3: Monitor for pests, such as aphids and cereal leaf beetles, and take appropriate action if necessary.</li><li>Step 4: Practice crop rotation and avoid continuous wheat cultivation in the same field.</li><li>Step 5: Follow recommended planting and harvesting practices for optimal yield and quality.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Wheat__septoria"><![CDATA[<h1>Septoria Leaf Spot in Wheat</h1><p>Septoria leaf spot is a fungal disease that affects wheat plants, causing small, oval-shaped lesions on leaves. To prevent and manage septoria leaf spot, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant wheat varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid excessive nitrogen fertilization, as it can increase disease susceptibility.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation and avoid continuous wheat cultivation in the same field.</li></ol>]]></string>

    <string name="Wheat__yellow_rust"><![CDATA[<h1>Yellow Rust in Wheat</h1><p>Yellow rust is a fungal disease that affects wheat plants, causing yellow or orange pustules on leaves and stems. To prevent and manage yellow rust, follow these steps:</p><ol><li>Step 1: Plant disease-resistant wheat varieties, if available.</li><li>Step 2: Avoid excessive nitrogen fertilization, as it can increase disease susceptibility.</li><li>Step 3: Apply fungicides according to the recommended schedule.</li><li>Step 4: Remove and destroy infected plant debris.</li><li>Step 5: Practice crop rotation and avoid continuous wheat cultivation in the same field.</li></ol>]]></string>


    <string-array name="filter_options">
        <item>All</item>
        <item>Edible</item>
        <item>Poisonous</item>
        <item>Indoor</item>
        <item>Indoor + Edible</item>
        <item>Indoor + Poisonous</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--    Notes-->

    <string name="Heading1">TITLE</string>
    <string name="Heading2">DESCRIPTION</string>
    <string name="hint1">Give some title</string>
    <string name="hint2">Give some description</string>
    <string name="channel_name">Reminder</string>
    <string name="channel_description">App Reminder and Alarm Notificaions</string>

</resources>